mobicity.com.au 2011-05-03

# Privacy | MobiCity

GloTech Ltd trades as MobiCity and is the owner of this site. This site and your data are transmitted via a 128-bit SSL secured link and stored in a secure database on our server. 

GloTech Ltd recognises the importance of your privacy and understands your concerns about the security of your personal information. We are committed to protecting any personal information about you that we hold. 

This privacy policy details how we generally manage your personal information and safeguard your privacy. These guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be made to this page. The National Privacy Principles from 21 December 2001 most private sector organisations in Australia must by law comply with the National Privacy Principles subject to the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) ("NPPs"). We are bound by the NPPs. 

Collecting personal information about you The kinds of personal information we hold: We only collect personal information that is necessary for us to perform our functions. 

The kinds of personal information we collect and hold will depend upon the services you request from us. However, it may include: 

Information you give us when you register your details with us on our website Information you give us when you register for a competition Information you give us when you communicate with or place an order from GloTech Ltd. We also collect some information from you when you use our website, www.mobicity.com.au and www.cameracity.com.au. Your use of the facilities and services available through our websites will determine the amount and type of information which we collect about you. 

Some of this information will not be personal information because it will not reveal your identity. 

The only personal information which we collect about you when you use our websites is what you tell us about yourself (for example, by completing an online form, subscribing to an online newsletter or placing an order), or information you provide to us when you send us an email. We may record your email address if you send us an email. 

We do not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose lists of MobiCity website users or other customers of GloTech Ltd. 

Collection of anonymous information 

As most websites do, we track usage patterns on our website on an anonymous aggregate basis. Your identity cannot reasonably be ascertained from this information. Each time you visit our website a web server makes a record of your visit. 

Using and disclosing your personal information The purposes for which we collect and hold personal information and how we use it. We respect your privacy. 

Any personal information which we collect about you will be used to provide the goods and services we normally provide in the course of our business. We do not sell or rent contact lists of our customers. 

We may use your personal information to contact you to discuss other matters relating to your service; for example, to conduct a survey or to analyse your usage and recommend a more appropriate plan. 

We may also use your personal information to provide you with information about other products and services offered by us. If you would prefer not to receive this information, please let us know by email to admin@stailsolutions.com.au (attn: Privacy Officer) or in writing to the address at the bottom of this page and we will respect your request. 

Contracting out services and disclosures. 

We may disclose your personal information to our service entities and contract out some of our functions (such as bulk mailing of MobiCity and telemarketing of subscription renewals) to external service providers. 

We may disclose your personal information to these external service providers but only so that they can provide the services that we have contracted out to them. 

Credit accounts 

If you have applied for a monthly credit account and we have approved your application, to the extent permitted by law we may share information about the status of your account with other credit providers and credit reporting agencies. 

Emails you receive from us regarding publications, products, events and education 

How we collect personal information from you 

If you provide us or have provided us with your email address, we may send emails to you containing GloTech Ltd information, such as newsletters. 

We may use an "email management system" to automate the management and dispatch of these emails. The system operates by inserting tracking codes in the emails that we send to you. 

The kind of personal information we collect about you 

The tracking code allows us to collect personal information about you, such as whether you received and opened an email, and whether you clicked through to any links to our website. This information that we collect about you will be stored by our email management system. If you have joined our customer base and wish to be removed from our list at any time in the future, please follow the links within the email newsletter to do so. We also use Google's remarketing system which utilise's cookies in your web browser to show you dedicated content through Google's content system. To disable this service please remove the cookie from your web browser. 

The purpose for which we collect the information about you 

The personal information that the email management system collects about you is used by us to: 

ensure that you only receive correspondence that you have informed us that you wish to receive determine whether the information that we send to you is suitable for your interests, information needs and profile ensure that the email address that you have provided us is still operational determine whether emails that we send to you are received by you update a request that you make to us to unsubscribe from a publication that we send to you review the effectiveness and relevance of our emails to you by collecting other statistical information 

Access to your personal information In most cases, you can gain access to personal information that we hold about you. 

We will handle requests for access to your personal information in accordance with the NPPs. 

We encourage all requests for access to your personal information to be directed to the Privacy Officer by email to admin@etailsolutions.com.au or by writing to the address below. 

We will deal with all requests for access to personal information as quickly as possible. 

Requests for a large amount of information, or information which is not currently in use, may require further time before a response can be given. 

If you would like to access details of the personal information held by Simply Mobiles Pty Ltd about you, please email the Privacy Officer at admin@mobicity.com.au or contact us in writing at the following address: 

Attn: Privacy Officer  
MobiCity  
1a, 36 Agnes St  
Fortitude Valley,   
QLD 4006
